# 哈喽大家好我是王刚
Hello, this is Chef Wang Gang.
# 本期视频我给大家分享
Today I will share a recipe with you:
# 如何快速腌咸蛋
Cured Duck Eggs (Easy Version)
# 首先我们准备新鲜的鸭蛋29个
First, we will get 29 fresh duck eggs.
# 放入盆中之后加入适量的清水
Add in some water after placing them in a bowl.
# 再加入白醋半瓶浸泡10分钟（约300克）
Add half a bottle of white vinegar (about 300 grams) into the water and soak the eggs for 10 minutes.
# 10分钟之后将鸭蛋清洗干净之后捞出备用
After 10 minutes, clean up the eggs.
# 加白醋浸泡的目的是方便去除鸭壳表面的鸭屎和杂质
Adding white vinegar will remove the faeces and dirt on the eggshells.
# 下一步我们开始准备辅料
Next, let's prepare other ingredients.
# 盆中加入八角几颗捏散备用
Add some star anises into the bowl.
# 加入适量的桂皮捏成小块备用
Break the cinnamons into small chunks and add them into the bowl.
# 再加入适量的青花椒
Then, we add some Sichuan green peppercorn.
# 然后加入适量的清水将香料清洗干净
Add in some water to rinse the spices.
# 这一步的目的是去除香料表面的灰尘
This step will remove the dirt on the spices.
# 清洗干净之后捞出备用
Take out the spices afterwards.
# 然后加入适量的高度白酒浸泡30分钟备用
Add some Baijiu (Chinese liquor) and soak the spices for an additional 30 minutes.
# 加白酒浸泡香料的目的是使其出味
Soaking the spices with Baijiu will bring out the aroma.
# 浸泡30分钟之后加入食用盐1000克搅拌均匀备用
After 30 minutes, add in 100 grams of salt and mix them together.
# 下一步我们开始准备裹鸭蛋
The next step is to wrap the eggs.
# 首先我们准备保鲜膜1大块
We need a large layer of plastic foil.
# 将调好的盐铺上一层
Spread a layer of pre-made salt evenly.
# 然后放上清洗干净的鸭蛋
Then, put the eggs on.
# 撒上适量的盐之后再均匀地裹起来即可
Spread some additional salt and wrap the foil around.
# 同学们裹得时候最好将两头稍微捏紧防止漏盐
We need to twist the sides tighly so that the salt won't come out.
# 下面大家再来仔细看一遍
Let's do this again.
# 鸭蛋裹好之后再放入瓦罐坛子中储存30天即可
We will seal the eggs into the jar for 30 days and they will be ready to eat.
# 同学们切记坛子不可放在暴晒的地方
We can't put the jar under the sun.
# 必须储存于避免阳光 阴暗的地方
It must be stored away from the sun.
# 30天之后将其取出煮熟之后即可食用
After 30 days, take out the eggs and boil them before serving.
# 一份简单快捷的咸鸭蛋就制作完成
A easy and fast version of cured duck eggs is complete.
# 下面开始技术总结
# 第一，同学们最好选择鸭蛋制作，咸蛋中只有鸭蛋最香油最多
# 第二，如果选择鸡蛋腌制，首先必须缩减时间，理论上鸡蛋只需要24天即可
# 第三，腌制咸蛋时盐必须给足，因为咸蛋不怕咸就怕盐不够
# 咸鸭蛋的技术总结完毕
Now, let's head to the technical summary:
First, it is recommended to use duck eggs, because they have the most oil.
Second, if we use normal eggs instead, we have to reduce the cure time to only 24 days.
Third, we have to use a generous amount of salt for better taste.
That's all for the technical summary.